<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-07-16T14:27:58+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Windows Apps London</title><subtitle>WinAppsLdn (Formerly Windows Phone User Group).
</subtitle><author><name>Matt Lacey</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2025/07/16/2014-10-13-Book-Review-Designing-Mobile-Payment-Experiences-Skip-Allums.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2025-07-16T14:27:58+00:00</published><updated>2025-07-16T14:27:58+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2025/07/16/2014-10-13-Book-Review-Designing-Mobile-Payment-Experiences%E2%80%93Skip-Allums</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2025/07/16/2014-10-13-Book-Review-Designing-Mobile-Payment-Experiences-Skip-Allums.html"><![CDATA[<p>Back in the late nineties I worked on a system that produced store gift cards/vouchers. Fast forward to 2008-9 and I was working on mobile payments, NFC payments, stored<br />
value cards on mobiles and even custom software for chip and pin terminals. More recently I’ve worked with a number of banks and money transfer services to build them mobile apps. (There are more than a couple of screenshots in the book that look <em>VERY</em> familiar!)<br />
All in all it’s fair to say I have an interest and background in working with mobile payment solutions.<br />
When I first heard about this book I became very interested. Mobile payment and money transfer is an area which I expect to grow considerably in the next few years and the recent announcements by Apple, with the iPhone 6, will only help fuel interest in this area and speed up growth.</p>

<p><a href="http://shop.oreilly.com/product/0636920029816.do"><img src="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-EWtqyyL-eWc/VDuVGhISReI/AAAAAAAAAys/-2HC6uPaKV0/s1600/designing-mob-pay-exp.gif" alt="" /></a></p>

<p>The book is relatively short at just 7 chapters and a little over 200 pages but it’s packed with useful information.</p>

<p>The first chapter starts the book by providing some background on the history of money and how and why it is used. It provides the perfect grounding for the rest of the book.</p>

<p>The second chapter introduces the three payment types covered in the book: NFC; Cloud : and Closed loop. The description of each of these is intermingled with a few UX notes dotted about. I think it would have been nicer to have made the UX points stand out more. As I am familiar with the payment options and their pros and cons I would have liked to see the UX tips stand out more form the text so I didn’t risk skipping over them as I skimmed a paragraph about a subject I am already familiar with.</p>

<p>The third chapter is the first to provide some easy take-aways for the reader. It analyses the strengths and weaknesses of the design, payments, feedback and security aspects of popular mobile payment solutions available today in the US. Namely Google Wallet, ISIS, PayPal, LevelUp, Starbucks and GoWallet.</p>

<p>The fourth chapter is about building trust into mobile payments. It was while reading this chapter that I realized I had been reading this book with my “developers hat” on, rather than one of a designer. I think of myself as a developer who wants to understand design. I also hope that more developers take an interest in design and how it impacts what they are developing. Anyway, this chapter diverged from what I was expecting and had a strong focus on the psychology of the consumer (or person using the app). I found it really useful to have this focus and the idea of designing for the most common security concerns people have with mobile payments was explored in depth in the rest of the chapter.</p>

<p>The fifth chapter is about actually designing successful payment interactions. The chapter is full of useful advice if creating an interaction using NFC, Bar or QR codes, or geolocation. It even made me smile as I remembered back to building an app that displayed barcodes on an iPhone and testing it in actual supermarkets. I’m sure with the information from this chapter I could revisit many past applications and create improvements. My only criticism would be that it would be nice to touch upon iBeacons or similar when also focusing on geolocation as that would, I suspect, address some of the issues of a geolocation approach. (e.g. getting the wrong neighboring store.)</p>

<p>Chapter six feels somewhat of a mish-mash of topics. This is probably due to the nature of the chapter being about additional services that can be provided with a payment experience to bring a richer and more valuable user engagement. Depending on the original app or services purpose is will affect what additional services are appropriate. This chapter provides guidance on: managing finances; rewarding loyalty; offers and coupons; and travel.</p>

<p>The final chapter looks to the future. As Apple has such an influence in the mobile space (especially in the US - the market this book focuses on) it is right that there is talk about what Apple may do. (This includes consideration for iBeacons-as noted earlier.) Then there’s speculation on what may come from MCX (the Merchant Customer Exchange) and Facebook. The chapter concludes with a look at wearable devices and bio-metrics and how they may be part of payment experiences in the future. As it’s still early days for these technologies the book provides no specific guidance in using them though.</p>

<p>All in all a useful book. If you are, or are likely to be working with mobile payment with regard to mobile devices and apps then I recommend you buy and read this book.</p>

<p>There is also a website by the author that contains additional content (via a blog) and a collection of mobile wallet &amp; payment UI design patterns: <a href="http://mobilepaymentux.com/">http://mobilepaymentux.com/</a></p>

<p><em>Disclaimer: The copy of this book was supplied for review as part of the <a href="http://www.oreilly.com/ug/">O’Reilly User Group/Community program</a>.</em></p>]]></content><author><name>Matt Lacey</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2025/07/16/2014-11-06-November-26th-Preparing-for-Windows-10.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2025-07-16T14:27:58+00:00</published><updated>2025-07-16T14:27:58+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2025/07/16/2014-11-06-November-26th-Preparing-for-Windows-10</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2025/07/16/2014-11-06-November-26th-Preparing-for-Windows-10.html"><![CDATA[<p>At the end of September <a href="http://blogs.windows.com/bloggingwindows/2014/09/30/announcing-windows-10/">Microsoft announced Windows 10</a>- the next version of Windows.<br />
This has implications for everyone building apps for Windows and Windows Phone (or who’s thinking about it).</p>

<p>We’ll look at what’s been said, what hasn’t, and make some reasonable assumptions about what we can take from this. We’ll start with a presentation but then open into a discussion about what developers and designers can do now. Come share your thoughts, plans and ideas, plus hear what others are thinking.</p>

<p>We’ll also look at the tools we’ll be using to build apps for Windows 10 - Visual Studio 14 and C#6.0.</p>

<p>And of course there will be the usual food, drink and networking.</p>

<p>Register on <a href="http://www.meetup.com/wpuguk/events/210456342/">MeetUp</a></p>]]></content><author><name>Matt Lacey</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2025/07/16/2014-11-12-Dev-17th-Xamarin-Re-Evolved-and-porting-from-Windows-Phone.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2025-07-16T14:27:58+00:00</published><updated>2025-07-16T14:27:58+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2025/07/16/2014-11-12-Dev-17th-Xamarin-Re-Evolved-and-porting-from-Windows-Phone</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2025/07/16/2014-11-12-Dev-17th-Xamarin-Re-Evolved-and-porting-from-Windows-Phone.html"><![CDATA[<p>In December (17th), we’ll be joined again by <a href="https://twitter.com/SoftSavage">Dominique Louis</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/micjames6">Michael James</a> from Xamarin.</p>

<p>They’ll be recapping the important announcements from the <a href="https://evolve.xamarin.com/">Evolve</a> conference and show us how to make the most of taking an app that is currently on Windows Phone and using Xamarin’s tools reach other platforms too.</p>

<p>As ever there’ll be an opportunity for you to share or demo what you’ve been working on too. Please get in touch if you have something to show.</p>

<p>Plus there will be food, drink and plenty of networking opportunities.</p>

<p>If you’re planning on coming it help us plan if you can please <a href="http://www.meetup.com/wpuguk/events/210456442/" title="Register on MeetUp">register</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name>Matt Lacey</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2025/07/16/2015-06-10-Badass-Making-Users-Awesome-Book-review.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2025-07-16T14:27:58+00:00</published><updated>2025-07-16T14:27:58+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2025/07/16/2015-06-10-Badass-Making-Users-Awesome%E2%80%93Book-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2025/07/16/2015-06-10-Badass-Making-Users-Awesome-Book-review.html"><![CDATA[<p>I feel I should start by apologising to you. I was given a review copy of this book a few months ago but the fact it’s taken me this long to tell you about it is something I should apologies for. You need to know about this book. And yes, I should apologies to the person who gave me the review copy too. ;)</p>

<p><img src="http://akamaicovers.oreilly.com/images/0636920036593/lrg.jpg" alt="Book Cover" /></p>

<p>This is a book about products and services but equally applies to apps. Given multiple similar apps, why are some more successful than others and what can we learn from the ones that are successful so that we can be successful too?</p>

<p>The structure and layout of the book is different to most but something you’ll recognize if you’ve read any of the <a href="http://shop.oreilly.com/category/series/head-first.do">Head First</a> series.</p>

<p>The book aims to provide a “formula for improving our chance of making a sustainable, bestselling product or service” or app!</p>

<p>I think there’s something in it for everyone involved in app development and who want to create apps that uses will love and get value from. Obviously if you’re just building apps for yourself and/or to scratch a technical itch then carry on. Well, actually, upon reflection, there’s still something in this book for you too.</p>

<p>Here’s the thing. When it comes to a product/service/app in any category or niche, what distinguishes the successful from the not so successful is not luck. It’s about making the person using it a badass!</p>

<p>What does that mean?</p>

<p>It’s about creating better users, not better products.</p>

<p>The knock on from this is that people will talk about themselves more (people like doing that) and the reason for that will be your app. The most trusted form of advertising is recommendations from friends and family members. When others discover that the reason for then becoming badass is down to your app you’ll see the number of downloads of your app go up.</p>

<p>You may have heard the advice that you should “build services, not apps”. While that advice is generally good, it’s better to not “build a better service, [but] make a better user of the service”.</p>

<p>If you can create your app so that it creates a great Post-UX UX (the experience after using the app) then you’re on your way to a winner.</p>

<p>The book has a lot of information to help you create apps (and services) that will help create badass users. That is users who “reliably perform in a superior way”.</p>

<p>The advice covers everything you’ll need to know to help your users. Whether it’s practice, examples, struggle, progress, rewards, jargon, choices, memorization, willpower or affordances. There is a lot you’ll need to know and this book will help you through it.</p>

<p>There are also two other things you’ll learn about that are especially close to my heart.</p>

<p>“Cake features” and how you app can actually make people fat. Yes really. And how you can cause an emotional response in your users through appropriate prompts and a compelling context.</p>

<p>I urge you. Go get and read this book to learn more.</p>

<p>You owe it to the people who will use the apps you help create.</p>

<p>Get it from <a href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/product/B00VAUIM18/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;camp=1634&amp;creative=19450&amp;creativeASIN=B00VAUIM18&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;tag=evedevshokno-21&amp;linkId=WYMA5KJCAPPOAJTU">Amazon</a> or <a href="http://shop.oreilly.com/product/0636920036593.do">O’Reilly</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name>Matt Lacey</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2025/07/16/2017-01-17-Feb-8-Creators-update-QA-with-Windows-engineers.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2025-07-16T14:27:58+00:00</published><updated>2025-07-16T14:27:58+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2025/07/16/2017-01-17-Feb-8-Creators-update-QA-with-Windows-engineers</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2025/07/16/2017-01-17-Feb-8-Creators-update-QA-with-Windows-engineers.html"><![CDATA[<p>We’re back. And starting 2017 in style!</p>

<p>This meeting coincides with the <a href="https://blogs.windows.com/buildingapps/2017/01/11/join-us-feb-8th-windows-developer-day-creators-update-livestream/">Windows Developer Day – Creators Update livestream</a> but there’s more. Not only will we be having a “viewing party” but we’ve also secured access to a Q&amp;A with members of the Windows engineering team straight after. <strong>This will be your opportunity to ask questions about what’s announced to the people who built it</strong>.</p>

<p>This will be your opportunity to see what’s new for developers in the Windows 10 Creators Update. We’ll watch and learn what it means for your apps and games, and more about Microsoft’s latest developer products. Information will cover updates in developing for the web or UWP, the latest consumer apps, and line-of-business tools.</p>

<p>While the live stream will be available online to anyone, the engineering team Q&amp;A is only accessible to those who attend the “viewing party” in person.</p>

<p>In addition to the exclusive Q&amp;A, we’ll provide some food and drink to all attending. Plus, we’ll have some goodies to give away too.</p>

<p>Timeline</p>

<p>16:45 - Doors open</p>

<p>17:00 - Live stream starts</p>

<p>18:30 - Engineering team Q&amp;A</p>

<p>19:30 - Creator update demos</p>

<p>20:30 - Home time :)</p>

<p>We know that these times may make it hard for some of you to attend the live stream but, hopefully, you’ll still be able to make it for the Q&amp;A 😉</p>

<p>If you’d like to attend, <a href="https://www.meetup.com/wpuguk/events/236970569/">please register on meetup</a> so we know how many to expect and cater for.</p>]]></content><author><name>Matt Lacey</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Meet the Windows Engineering team in London</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/Meet-the-Windows-Engineering-team-in-London" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Meet the Windows Engineering team in London" /><published>2017-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/Meet-the-Windows-Engineering-team-in-London</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/Meet-the-Windows-Engineering-team-in-London"><![CDATA[<p>The <a href="https://blogs.windows.com/buildingapps/2017/09/14/windows-developer-day-returns/">Windows Developer Day</a> returns on October 10th and it’s being broadcast from London.</p>

<p>There isn’t room for us to attend the broadcast (I asked several times) but we are able to go one better.</p>

<p>On the next day  (<strong>Wednesday 11th October</strong>) we’ll be joined by the members of the Windows engineering team who made the announcements for a special social, Q&amp;A event. You’ll be able to ask them your questions about what was announced and anything to do with developing for the Fall (Autumn) Creators Update.</p>

<p>After the last developer day we had a “viewing party” with a Skype Q&amp;A straight after the keynote and there was a lot of feedback that you would have preferred more time to reflect on the announcement before asking questions. Hopefully, 24 hours will be enough. There will also be the opportunity to ask any other questions of the team and it’ll be great to meet up as a group again for the first time in a few months.</p>

<p><strong>If you’d like to come, <a href="https://www.meetup.com/wpuguk/events/243674562/">please register on Meetup</a></strong> and we’ll look forward to seeing you there.</p>]]></content><author><name>Matt Lacey</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Windows Developer Day returns on October 10th and it’s being broadcast from London.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How was it for you?</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/How-was-it-for-you" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How was it for you?" /><published>2017-09-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-09-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/How-was-it-for-you</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/How-was-it-for-you"><![CDATA[<p>I know the group’s been very quiet for a while. And, even though life’s been getting in the way, I’ve not forgotten about it.<br />
There’s a possibility of something later in the year (more details when I have them) but for now, I have a question for you.<br />
It doesn’t matter if you came to one meeting or dozens.<br />
You may have been to the recent meetings or not been for years.<br />
Whatever your situation, I’d love to hear from you.</p>

<p><strong>How, why, and was attending past meetings a good thing for you?</strong></p>

<p>I have my own thoughts based on “running” the group for 7+ years and had lots of positive and a few negative experiences along the way. (Maybe I’ll share them if you’re interested.) But, good or bad, I want to hear from you.</p>

<p>Here are a few deeper questions if you have the time to give a longer answer but any response will be appreciated.</p>

<ul>
  <li>Did you come just out of curiosity and to gain wider knowledge?</li>
  <li>Was it a way to learn or hear about something specific?</li>
  <li>Did you come with specific goals from attending? and were those goals met or achieved?</li>
  <li>Was it just an opportunity to pass the time with some free beer and pizza?</li>
  <li>Did the promise of freebies (SWAG) impact your choice to attend?</li>
  <li>How would your apps (and even your life) be different if you’d not come or the meetings had never happened?</li>
  <li>Is what you learned at past meetings still relevant or have you moved onto other things with no direct connection to Windows [Phone] apps?</li>
  <li>What persuaded you to come the first time?</li>
  <li>If you were nervous about attending at any time, why?</li>
  <li>Did anything happen or change to stop you wanting to come back?</li>
  <li>Would future meetings be interesting to you?</li>
  <li>What was the best thing about having attended in the past?</li>
  <li>Which meeting and for what reason (subject, speaker, location, whatever) was your favourite?</li>
</ul>

<p>Thanks</p>

<p>matt.</p>]]></content><author><name>Matt Lacey</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know the group’s been very quiet for a while. And, even though life’s been getting in the way, I’ve not forgotten about it. There’s a possibility of something later in the year (more details when I have them) but for now, I have a question for you. It doesn’t matter if you came to one meeting or dozens. You may have been to the recent meetings or not been for years. Whatever your situation, I’d love to hear from you.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WPUG Alumni on the Gone Mobile podcast</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/WPUG-Alumni-on-the-Gone-Mobile-podcast" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WPUG Alumni on the Gone Mobile podcast" /><published>2017-05-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-05-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/WPUG-Alumni-on-the-Gone-Mobile-podcast</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/WPUG-Alumni-on-the-Gone-Mobile-podcast"><![CDATA[<p>This was totally unplanned but three of the last four guests on the Gone Mobile Podcast will be familiar to you if you were a regular attendee of WPUG meetings.</p>

<p><a href="http://gonemobile.io/"><img src="http://gonemobile.io/images/Gone.Mobile.Header.Logo.png" alt="GoneMobile.io" /></a></p>

<p>Listen and enjoy:</p>

<p><a href="http://gonemobile.io/blog/e0047.building.reactive.apps.with.xamarin.forms.and.fsharp.with.rob.lyndon/">Gone Mobile 47: Building Reactive Apps with Xamarin.Forms and F# with Rob Lyndon</a></p>

<p><a href="http://gonemobile.io/blog/e0049.bot.framework.with.david.hamilton/">Gone Mobile 49: Bot Framework with David Hamilton</a></p>

<p><a href="http://gonemobile.io/blog/e0050.building.great.app.experiences.with.matt.lacey/">Gone Mobile 50: Building Great App Experiences with Matt Lacey</a></p>]]></content><author><name>Matt Lacey</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This was totally unplanned but three of the last four guests on the Gone Mobile Podcast will be familiar to you if you were a regular attendee of WPUG meetings.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">March 21 – Windows App Developers and the Future</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/March-21%E2%80%93Windows-App-Developers-and-the-Future" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="March 21 – Windows App Developers and the Future" /><published>2017-05-06T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-05-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/March-21%E2%80%93Windows-App-Developers-and-the-Future</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/March-21%E2%80%93Windows-App-Developers-and-the-Future"><![CDATA[<p>In a break from the pattern of past meetings, on March 21st we’ll be having a series of discussions of what the future for Windows App developers looks like.</p>

<p>Join us for a pub lunch to discuss how you see things going.</p>

<p>Can’t make lunch? Join us for coffee in the afternoon to share your opinions or ideas.</p>

<p>Not free until the evening? Join us and the Azure User Group to hear how bots might be the future.</p>

<p>More details, etc. at <a href="https://www.meetup.com/wpuguk/events/238111110/">https://www.meetup.com/wpuguk/events/238111110/</a></p>]]></content><author><name>Matt Lacey</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a break from the pattern of past meetings, on March 21st we’ll be having a series of discussions of what the future for Windows App developers looks like.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What happens when you get 25 developers in a room for a day? (Submit-It!)</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/What-happens-when-you-get-25-developers-in-a-room-for-a-day-Submit-It" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What happens when you get 25 developers in a room for a day? (Submit-It!)" /><published>2015-11-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2015-11-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/What-happens-when-you-get-25-developers-in-a-room-for-a-day-Submit-It</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/What-happens-when-you-get-25-developers-in-a-room-for-a-day-Submit-It"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/5/c/4/600_444154244.jpeg" alt="Submit-It! attendees" /></p>

<p>A. They submit 25 apps to the store.</p>

<p>Well that’s <a href="http://www.meetup.com/wpuguk/events/225592021/">what we did on the Saturday just gone</a>. There were a mixture of new apps, apps updated to support Windows 10 (mobile and desktop as a single UWP) and other updates to existing Windows8.1 and Windows Phone apps.<br />
These are (most of–some are stuck in certification) the apps in question.</p>

<table>
  <thead>
    <tr>
      <th> </th>
      <th> </th>
      <th> </th>
    </tr>
  </thead>
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-gb/store/apps/tembler/9wzdncrfjtnc"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.12770.9007199266274576.c2372ac7-aa72-4a0a-8d26-09db0394e719.2bfd3d64-9351-4fe9-bf9e-d83257c5d226?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="Tembler" /></a></td>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-gb/store/apps/simple-maths/9nblggh69l7t"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.57406.13510798886691084.22040f0c-a19c-4402-aa5f-bda0ba4dcabe.cbb8e2c2-3095-4416-a73a-8fd8b4179e71?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="Simple Maths" /></a></td>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-gb/store/apps/izaaks-favourite-things/9nblggh3gpk6"><img src="https://store-images.microsoft.com/image/apps.42375.13510798884269663.a03a3da1-4322-4122-83c2-4fd67f43afa7.6eb96b13-ba52-4f6e-aa45-27af40067d34?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="Izaak's Favourite Things" /></a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-gb/store/apps/fun-basic/9nblggh168n7"><img src="https://store-images.microsoft.com/image/apps.21969.13510798882430104.6372d930-5ec8-423f-a53e-dfb2a65dc14b.83192f9b-0aef-4e9a-a18e-d677c4001a56?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="Fun Basic" /></a></td>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9NBLGGH69PF0"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.25819.13510798886693621.ca61b867-64fb-4014-9941-f849ae314fd6.7c3a406b-94c6-46ee-9843-520de83d80c5?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="BasketCoach Stats" /></a></td>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9nblggh69g09"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.3285.13510798886694942.b30b5287-e0c4-4e75-8fe5-9286e52bf1bd.2bf70022-9397-4b16-a5ff-50beb8da8e37?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="ParisNewsUpdate" /></a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9nblggh69fv7"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.22979.13510798886695320.911cb259-faed-44dc-baa0-2b39182152b5.aa939375-4b4c-49ea-a873-c25f803dddf0?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="Quick! Theme my band!" /></a></td>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-GB/store/apps/Soundicity/9NBLGGH0G0HF"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.44712.13510798882998680.785d1940-144e-48f5-9f19-998753e24116.eaf0b82f-da1c-4201-a4f2-aedac4691679?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="Soundicity" /></a></td>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9nblggh69mpp"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.64986.13510798886694120.479e3bb5-457c-42ae-b6b9-798d5362f5fb.97941363-b19c-4774-8fa1-5f327a16f3ed?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="SEPic" /></a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9wzdncrdr8rz"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.25164.9007199266547248.e2bb46d1-4569-4894-85dd-ad72e8e225c6.00b520df-f602-4ad5-9d26-fae351ed5c76?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="My Shelf" /></a></td>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9nblggh69fr5"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.17364.13510798886695364.a1ace402-5b40-4f05-851b-ad7f3c260b79.12337e92-f3d4-43f9-9d37-7a8c26010860?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="Have I been p0wned?" /></a></td>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9nblggh69fqz"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.59841.13510798886695418.aca90a1d-629b-443b-b45c-74b56b6b8aef.dffd9340-f294-41d4-bd7f-36b0baaba7e8?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="Mqtt Monitor" /></a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9nblggh68tjs"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.41797.13510798886679035.1fca634b-d707-4c3f-98a2-597efd56fdd9.25a3e660-5599-48b1-aa62-50f26566e2ea?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="Video Games Vault" /></a></td>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9nblggh69gk2"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.44510.13510798886695447.c9018d24-dcfa-4935-822d-6f136c72cadc.abf54952-4fa6-4550-8eed-039c38b5db75?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="Turtled" /></a></td>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9nblggh69GN3"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.52794.13510798886695596.06359cc7-2de8-4dd8-a35c-d4433fbd633c.cae7623f-a5ff-4324-b37f-f3ff9884ebb7?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="PS15" /></a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9nblggh69gn7"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.618.13510798886695592.cc8fc38e-1fb0-4d7b-bccd-e1630a1f87b2.935ffbed-c8c3-4875-8b84-fe1968207da5?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="Films to watch lite" /></a></td>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9nblggh3ltt5"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.38703.13510798884382064.58b5c8cc-07c5-454c-8f88-ef827d6ea675.59b07eb4-4987-4cc0-9ba4-6bae9c1152ae?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="Bikometer" /></a></td>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9nblggh68cpc"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.61071.13510798886659722.d0df340c-40f6-456a-af96-ecf3ffca8291.18bec2ae-d647-4a93-b3b0-919a09d5323c?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="Cineworld Film Showings" /></a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9nblggh3g59m"><img src="https://store-images.microsoft.com/image/apps.62581.13510798884263794.3d9135d0-5ea6-4b9f-935d-4df2c19fccf7.0ef3db65-de72-495c-bd35-f334ec6ba26a?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="Hexpand" /></a></td>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9nblggh69gkm"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.34578.13510798886695654.f1767e10-2910-4dea-a89e-0387cc7e4963.ef7b38a0-a842-43c0-be7f-c4aee180947f?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="TechnoBapple" /></a></td>
      <td><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9nblggh69pdg"><img src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.60237.13510798886693605.9e01597b-9032-4607-b8e7-7dcc9a15ce62.3d949989-3cd7-4067-8824-b4c833f06de0?w=191&amp;h=191" alt="Quiz-Me" /></a></td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>]]></content><author><name>Matt Lacey</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry></feed>